<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

	<title>Hank Quinlan's Blog</title>
	<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog"/>
	<updated>2019-03-04T16:59:39+01:00</updated>
	<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog</id>
	<author>
		<name>Hank Quinlan</name>
		<email>hankquinlanhub@gmail.com</email>
	</author>

	
		<entry>
			<title>Skialp at Chopok</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2016/03/14/skialp-Chopok"/>
			<updated>2016-03-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2016/03/14/skialp-Chopok</id>
			<content type="html">My unckle take me to the skialp for the first time in my life. Skialp differ from basic skiing in the equipment and especially in skis
and ski boots. Skis are lighter than ordinary one build for the slope and they have to have mechanism for skialp ski boots. The mechanism 
enables skier to have free heel and therefore he can move similarly as in the cross country skiing and at the way down it is firm so skier
can safely ski down from the mountain. I had enjoyed it very much.</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Skialp at Chopok</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2016/03/14/skialp-Chopok"/>
			<updated>2016-03-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2016/03/14/skialp-Chopok</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;
My uncle take me to the skialp for the first time in my life. Maybe some of you have not idea what skialp is. For you a little explanation.
Skialp differ from basic skiing in the equipment and especially in skis and ski boots. Skis are lighter than ordinary one build for the slope 
and they have to have mechanism for skialp ski boots. The mechanism enables skier to have free heel and therefore he can move similarly as 
in the cross country skiing and at the way down it is firm so skier
can safely ski down from the mountain.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/IMAG1255.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chopok&quot; style=&quot;width:71%; height:40%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
As first we had climb to Milan Rastislav Štefánik cottage. Our energy has dropped after this ascend and we need to reacharge it so we stay at
lunch and relax a bit. In the way 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Trakai castle in Lithuania</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2015/04/30/trakai-baltic-castle"/>
			<updated>2015-04-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2015/04/30/trakai-baltic-castle</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This is Trakai island - literally castle on the water.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	

</feed>