<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

	<title>Hank Quinlan's Blog</title>
	<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog"/>
	<updated>2019-03-07T10:30:46+01:00</updated>
	<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog</id>
	<author>
		<name>Hank Quinlan</name>
		<email>hankquinlanhub@gmail.com</email>
	</author>

	
		<entry>
			<title>Rome</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/rome"/>
			<updated>2018-11-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/rome</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Rome is a classical place for tourists in summer. September is ideal due to pleasant weather and the acceptable prices due to end of summer holidays. 
I would want to main atractions as well as the less popular places such as Roman catacombs and vatican gardens(yes those gardens). In case you are interest write
me to my email jan.hajzok@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>London</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/london"/>
			<updated>2018-11-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/london</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;London has quite a lot of interesting points of interests. I have seen the trafitional monuments and this time I would want to visit less famous places.
Last time I was in London I didn’t have time for Warner Bros. Studio, where Harry Potter was filmed, Sea life, Madame Tussauds and history museum.
This is everything I want to see, but if you write me to jan.hajzok@gmail.com with your recommendations, maybe I will reconsider itinerary.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Mont Blanc</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/mont-blanc"/>
			<updated>2018-11-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/mont-blanc</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It was in my viewfinder for a long time and finally I got opportunity. The climb is not as hard as it look like. 
It is recommended to have basic climb gear and to have experiance with using it. If you are not afraid write me 
to my email jan.hajzok@gmail.com or with the plugin at the below.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Skialp at Chopok</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/skialp-Chopok"/>
			<updated>2018-11-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/11/23/skialp-Chopok</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/IMAG1255.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chopok&quot; style=&quot;width:71%; height:40%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
My uncle take me to the skialp for the first time in my life. Maybe some of you have not idea what skialp is. For you a little explanation.
Skialp differ from basic skiing in the equipment and especially in skis and ski boots. Skis are lighter than ordinary one build for the slope 
and they have to have mechanism for skialp ski boots. The mechanism enables skier to have free heel and therefore he can move similarly as 
in the cross country skiing and at the way down it is firm so skier
can safely ski down from the mountain.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/IMAG1254.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;uncle&quot; style=&quot;width:40%; height:71%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
As first we had climb to Milan Rastislav Štefánik cottage. Our energy has dropped after this ascend and we need to reacharge it, so we stay at
lunch and relax a bit. Our next target was hill call Ďumbier. It was neccesary to go through it because it's on the ridge leading to our destiantion.
At the top of hill is a big metal double cross which symbolize our country. For those who don't know double cross in our nation sign and flag. 
After that we went couple times downhills and uphills until we came to the Chopok hill, our destination, in the altitude of 2048  m a.s.l. Even
thoug it was thick fog and we had see just over 20 metres in distance, it was wonderful feeling. 
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Trakai castle in Lithuania</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/07/30/trakai-baltic-castle"/>
			<updated>2018-07-30T00:00:00+02:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/07/30/trakai-baltic-castle</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/IMAG0010.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trakai_outside&quot; style=&quot;width:71%; height:40%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
	The castle origins began in second half of the 14 century and it was meant to be a fortress. It has several
	defence systems such as hudge walland and very convienant place in the middle of the lake. Only way how
	you can get to the castle is on thewooden bridge or at boat. Castle itself has several courtyards where
	are being held Middle Age presentations such as knight fights or market from that era. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/pilis0001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;trakai_inside&quot; style=&quot;width:71%; height:40%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
		</entry>
	
		<entry>
			<title>Snake game</title>
			<link href="http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/03/15/snake-game"/>
			<updated>2018-03-15T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
			<id>http://hankquinlan.github.io/blog/2018/03/15/snake-game</id>
			<content type="html">&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/snake2.png&quot; alt=&quot;snake1&quot; style=&quot;width:70%; height:70%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
It was a lot of fun during the process of coding this very basic game. I learned a lot about how the graphics 
rendering works in the OpenGL engine. I apply my skills from the subject in which we learned to code in the
notoriusly famous programming language C++.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;/pictures/snake1.png&quot; alt=&quot;snake2&quot; style=&quot;width:70%; height:70%;&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

</content>
		</entry>
	

</feed>